Under the moon light a
sleek black cat prowls silently
its amber eyes glowing mysteriously.
The playful orange cat leaps
joyfully, chasing butterflies, its fur
gleaming like a fiery sunset.
The tuxedo cat, clad in
striking black and white, moves
with confidence. Its curious whiskers
twitch as it playfully explores,
radiating charm and mischief.
The Siamese cat, with its
sleek cream coat and dark
points, exudes grace and intelligence
Its mesmerising blue eyes gleam
with curiosity and its soft
melodic meows captivate all Known
for its affectionate nature it
bonds deeply becoming a loyal
and enchanting companion.
A serene white cat lounges
gracefully, blending into snowy drifts,
eyes reflecting icy blue skies.